[{"answer": "Ow!   What?", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " my friend, I'll be there in half an hour..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What mission", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Good morning sir", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "So am I, sir", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "From the mission file I've read, this is one of those things that whips out from the wall, grabs your head and r", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Sort of", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "No obviously not. I don't want this to sound like a terribly sel", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Why me", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " you are so wrong. It's a perfect analogy. my friend as Goa'uld", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You are so shallow", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "All right that does it. You know the entire VHS collection was going to one of you.  It's going to my friend. He gets it.  Thank God. Pizza.  Well you're not the usual delivery boy", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "It's always a good time for you sir. Come on in. Let me get you a chair", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Okay. but I'm hoping you of all people, won't jump to conclusions", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Someone like me", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Hey I'm not saying that everything that has been going on around here is right, I mean we have no right to play God, but neither do the Goa'uld. Now I know none of this may seem real to you on paper, but trust me, they're pure evil. Now if they had the chance they would either destroy us or enslave us all. You can read as many mission reports as you want but before you decide what should or shouldn't be done around here, why don't you go through that gate and see what's going on for yourself", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "We may not have good time and my friend certainly doesn't", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Colonel my friend, my friend, Teal'c.  I know these are strange circumstances to be meeting for the first time", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " I am ... Dr my friend, Colonel", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You just said derantis", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Did to", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Wait a minute, I thought you didn't buy into the whole invasion thing", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I know where it is.", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "The fact is, until we know the location of the Lost City..", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You know where it is now", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "This is my office, this is my chair. Until someone tells me otherwise, I'm going to make decisions as I see fit. Not as they fit into your agenda.", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Whatever your agenda is", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I will see you soon my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Lost-City-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "In fact it is you who knows something I do not", "qsentId": 30}]